OK, what we're getting ready to do now is to start our first braid.
And just like and French braid, you're going to grab a piece of hair, only this time it's a much smaller amount because we're working with less hair, and you're going to divide it up in three's.
And when it comes to any type of stylized braiding, generally we do an out braid, so we're going to go under and go under, and I'm going to go under one more time.
I like to leave it with a good start so I can get a good hold on it.
Get all the hair out the way, just grab anther little piece and add it there and go underneath.
Now, when it comes to these smaller braids you really want to make sure you've got a good grip on it to keep your braid in line.
Go ahead and grab that piece and go under, and try to keep your strand separate.
With longer hair it takes a bit more work because you're really got a bit further way to stretch to separate your hair all the way out.
OK, and just keep running your fingers through the hair to keep it untangled, and you'll just keep adding hair to it as we move along down the braid.
Just continue alternating sides, adding hair and crossing underneath until we get all the way to the bottom.